$FHU_SETTINGS	Settings
$FHU_ACTOR_LIST	Inflated actors
$FHU_ENABLED	Inflation enabled
$FHU_FEMALE_ENABLED	Female Inflation enabled
$FHU_MALE_ENABLED	Male Inflation enabled
$FHU_MIN_TIME	Minimum inflation time
$FHU_HOURS	{0} hours
$FHU_MAX_AMOUNT	Maximum inflation amount
$FHU_ORALMAX_AMOUNT	Maximum oral inflation amount
$FHU_TULL_CREAMPIE_THRESHOLD	Animated creampie threshold
	Animated creampie threshold
$FHU_ADD_RACE	Add race
$FHU_LOGGING	Enable debug logging
$FHU_RESET_ACTORS	Reset all actors
$FHU_RESET	Reset
$FHU_RACE_AMOUNT	Humanoid Cum Amount
$FHU_RACE_AMOUNTS	Humanoid cum amounts
$FHU_CREATURERACE_AMOUNT	Creature Cum Amount
$FHU_CREATURERACE_AMOUNTS	Creature cum amounts
$FHU_VAG_AMOUNT	Vaginal cum amount
$FHU_AN_AMOUNT	Anal cum amount
$FHU_OR_AMOUNT	Oral cum amount
$FHU_TOTAL_INF	Total inflation
$FHU_MORPHSTRING	Inflation Morph 01
$FHU_MORPHSTRING_HELP	Enter a slider name you want to apply when you are inflated. No oral cum related. \nDefault string set to "PregnancyBelly". Not mandatory.
$FHU_MORPHSTRING2	Inflation Morph 02
$FHU_MORPHSTRING2_HELP	Enter a second slider name you want to apply when you are inflated. No oral cum related. Not mandatory
$FHU_MORPHSTRING3	Inflation Morph 03
$FHU_MORPHSTRING3_HELP	Enter a third slider name you want to apply when you are inflated. No oral cum related. Not mandatory
$FHU_MORPHSTRING4	Inflation Morph Oral
$FHU_MORPHSTRING4_HELP	Enter a slider name you want to apply when you are inflated by oral cum. Not mandatory
$FHU_MORPHSTRING_DUPLICATION	The string value you just typed is not available as it's already used. Try another one.
$FHU_SURE	Are you sure?
$FHU_DONE	Done
$FHU_MIN_TIME_HELP	Minimum time from the last fill up until characters start expelling the cum.\nSeparate timers for anal and vaginal sex.
$FHU_MAX_AMOUNT_HELP	Maximum amount to scale the character belly node to from being filled in one hole.\nWith both holes filled, the maximum is 1.2 times this.
$FHU_ORALMAX_AMOUNT_HELP	Maximum amount of oral cum.
$FHU_TULL_CREAMPIE_THRESHOLD_HELP	Minimum filled percentage to equip Animated Creampie items.
	Minimum filled percentage to equip Animated Creampie items.
$FHU_LOGGING_HELP	Enables debug logging into a log file to help troubleshooting.\nThe file can be found in \\Documents\\My Games\\Skyrim\\Logs\\Script\\ if logging is enabled in Skyrim.ini\nINCLUDE THESE LOGS WHEN ASKING FOR HELP/REPORTING ISSUES IN THE FORUMS!
$FHU_RESET_HELP	Resets the inflation on all affected actors, also making this mod safe-ish to uninstall
$FHU_ADD_RACE_HELP	Add a custom race to the race list by targeting a character of that race and pressing this key.\nHold the key down for a second or more to add the player characters race.
$FHU_ENABLED_HELP	Enables or disables inflation and other features. Disabling the mod will also reset all inflated actors.\nTo uninstall the mod cleanly, disable this before removing any files.
$FHU_FEMALE_ENABLED_HELP	Enables or disables inflation on female actors.\nDisabling will not affect already inflated actors, but will prevent further inflation.
$FHU_MALE_ENABLED_HELP		Enables or disables inflation on male actors.\nDisabling will not affect already inflated actors, but will prevent further inflation.
$FHU_BURST_TICK	Your cum-bursting belly is painfully impossible to ignore
$FHU_BURST_END	You let out a sight of relief as the cum drains even a little
$FHU_BURST_START01	You're filled to burst with cum!
$FHU_BURST_START02	You're painfully inflated past your limits with cum!
$FHU_ACTORS_RESET	Inflated actors reset
$FHU_ANIM_MULT	Animation length multiplier
$FHU_ANIM_MULT_HELP	Multiplier for the deflate animation duration. With the default 1.0, animations last between 4 and 8 seconds. Multiplier of 10.0 would then make them last between 40 and 80 seconds for example.
$FHU_ENCUMBER	Encumber actors
$FHU_ENCUMBER_HELP	Slows down actors depending on how full of cum they are.
$FHU_DEF_ABILITY	Expel cum
$FHU_DEF_ABILITY_HELP	Try to expel the cum inside you. The ability is active while the key is held down and requires stamina to use. Stops when you either stop pressing the key, stamina runs out or the pool is fully drained.
$FHU_DEF_FIZZLE	You are too exhausted to attempt that now.
$FHU_DEF_BLOCK	The plugs inside you make it impossible to push any of the cum out
$FHU_DEF_BLOCK_A	The anal plug inside you prevents you from pushing the cum out
$FHU_DEF_BLOCK_V	The vaginal plug inside you prevents you from pushing the cum out
$FHU_DEF_FAIL	Despite your best efforts, you fail to push the cum out
$FHU_DEF_BURST_FAIL	All the pain prevents you from pushing the cum out
$FHU_DEF_ORAL_FAIL	You tried to vomit but there left only bad taste in your mouth.
$FHU_DEF_NOCUM	You tried to push out cum but there is no left
$FHU_BASE_SCALE	Normal belly scale
$FHU_BASE_SCALE_HELP	The belly scale to start inflating from, and reset the scale to after inflation.\nDefault is 1.0\nSet to a negative value to use whatever scale the inflated actor has at the start of inflation.
$FHU_ANIM_DEFLATE	Play Deflation Animations
$FHU_ANIM_DEFLATE_HELP	Toggles the deflation animations\nThis includes fluid effects, animations, and armor stripping\nGlobal to all actors
$FHU_STATUS_MESSAGES	Status messages
$FHU_STATUS_MESSAGES_HELP	Enables displaying periodic status messages about your state while inflated.
$FHU_STATUS_MESSAGES_CHANCE	Status message chance
$FHU_STATUS_MESSAGES_CHANCE_HELP	The chance of a status message showing up each hour.
$FHU_NPC_COMMENTS	Toggle NPC Comments
$FHU_NPC_COMMENTS_HELP	Toggles comments by NPCs around Skyrim\nNOTE: I'm unsure whether this affects followers. Let me know.\nRemind me to fix this help message later, thanks.
$FHU_BURST_WEAPON_DROP	The cramps are too painful to keep a hold of your weapons.
$FHU_BURST_SPELL_DROP	The cramps are too painful to keep up your concentration.
$FHU_CUM_MULT	Cum amount multiplier
$FHU_CUM_MULT_HELP	The race cum amounts are multiplied by this before applying any inflation, making it easier to globally adjust the cum amounts.\nDefault is 1.00.
$FHU_EVENTS_HEADER	Events
$FHU_EVENTS	Events enabled
$FHU_EVENTS_HELP	Enables periodic events like status messages, event probabilities can also be changed individually.
$FHU_EVENT_INTERVAL	Event interval
$FHU_EVENT_INTERVAL_HELP	Time between event loops in game hours.
$FHU_PLUGGED_VAG_1	The vaginal plug keeps you inflated
$FHU_PLUGGED_AN_1	The anal plug keeps you inflated
$FHU_PLUGGED_VAG_2	The vaginal plug keeps you painfully inflated
$FHU_PLUGGED_AN_2	The anal plug keeps you painfully inflated
$FHU_PLUGGED_VAG_3	Despite all the excruciating cramping, the vaginal plug keeps you filled.
$FHU_PLUGGED_AN_3	Despite all the excruciating cramping, the anal plug keeps you filled.
$FHU_EVENT_PLUGGED	Plugged!
$FHU_EVENT_PLUGGED_HELP	Extra status messages and effects if plugged and inflated.
$FHU_STRIP	Strip chest armor
$FHU_STRIP_HELP	Strips chest armor during deflation.
$FHU_CUM_EFFECTS	Enable cum effects
$FHU_CUM_EFFECTS_HELP	Enables cum debuffs & buffs based on the races the player character has had sex with.\nThe effects disappear once the cum is gone.
$FHU_CONSOLE_PRINT	Console statuses
$FHU_CONSOLE_PRINT_HELP	Print status messages in console in addition to the screen corner.
$FHU_VISUAL_BELLY	Enable belly growing
$FHU_VISUAL_BELLY_HELP	Enables visible growing of the belly on characters. Disabling will stop FHU from changing the belly scale completely.
$FHU_RESETQUEST_HELP	Reset the entire quests
$FHU_RESET_QUEST	ResetQuests
$FHU_RESETQUEST	Reset
$FHU_Compatibility	Compatible Mods
$FHU_BeeingFemale	Beeing Female
$FHU_BeeingFemaleInfo	The amount of cum in your womb will affect the chance of being impreganted in Beeing Female. Also with your womb inflated(about 70%) by cum, regardless of the cycle, you can be impregnated with high chance.
$FHU_Fertility	Fertility
$FHU_FertilityInfo	The amount of cum in your womb will affect the chance of being impreganted in Fertility. Also with your womb inflated(about 70%) by cum, regardless of the cycle, you can be impregnated with high chance.
$Installed	Installed
$NotInstalled	Not Installed
$FHU_PlacePuddles	Cum Puddle
$FHU_SFU_PlacePuddles_HELP	Place cum puddles where an actor deflates.
$FHU_BodyMorph	Body Morph
$FHU_BodyMorph_Help	Enable Body Morph Scale instead of NIO Bone Scale. If you are a LE user, disable it. However if you are a SE user, enable it.
$FHU_BODYMORPH_APPLY_PERIOD	Body morph apply period
$FHU_BODYMORPH_APPLY_PERIOD_HELP	How often body morph updates are applied.
$FHU_Tongue_EFFECT	TongueWhenExpelCum
$FHU_Tongue_EFFECT_HELP	Actor pulls out her tongue when she expels cum.
$FHU_OnEventSpermPC_EFFECT	OnEventAddSpermPC
$FHU_OnEventSpermPC_EFFECT_HELP	If some amount of cum stays unremoved from Player's womb, send events to other prgnancy mods. It doesn't mean the effect is applied to Player immediately.
$FHU_OnEventSpermNPC_EFFECT	OnEventAddSpermNPC
$FHU_OnEventSpermNPC_EFFECT_HELP	If some amount of cum stays unremoved from NPC's womb, send events to other prgnancy mods. This can be script-heavy depending on how many actors the pregnancy mods are tracking.
$FHU_AUTO_DEFLATE	No Auto Deflation
$FHU_AUTO_DEFLATE_HELP	No actors automatically deflate cum periodically. Plugs will prevent it from being oozed through holes.
$FHU_ABSORB_SPERM	Absorb Sperm
$FHU_ABSORB_SPERM_HELP	The function is only available when auto deflation is off. Sperm will be absorbed in her womb gradually and arousal stat will increase as well.  However plugs will prevent it from being absorbed. 
$FHU_ABSORB_SPERMORAL	Digest Sperm
$FHU_ABSORB_SPERMORAL_HELP	The function is only available when Absorb Sperm is on. Sperm will be digested in her stomach gradually when you do not vomit.
$FHU_FOLLOWER_COMMENTS	Toggle Follower Comments
$FHU_FOLLOWER_COMMENTS_HELP	Toggles comments by Followers.
$FHU_ARMOR_SLOTS	UnStrip Armor Slots
$FHU_VARIOUSCUMINGREDIENTS	Cum ingredients
$FHU_VARIOUSCUMINGREDIENTS_HELP	Get cum ingredients when deflating. 
$FHU_VARIOUSCUM	Cum Variations
$FHU_VARIOUSCUM_HELP	Enable various cum effects according to a last actor in a sexlab scene.
$FHU_DEFLATE_CHANCE	Deflate Fail Chance
$FHU_DEFLATE_CHANCE_HELP	The chance to fail to expel cum.
$FHU_TOGGLESLOT_HELP	Ignore toggled-on slots when stripping.
$FHU_STATUS_MOANING	Moaning Sound
$FHU_STATUS_MOANING_HELP	Actor moans when deflating.
$FHU_SEXLAB_MOANING	Sexlab Moaning Sound
$FHU_SEXLAB_MOANING_HELP	Use the moaning sound from Sexlab instead of the one from the mod.
$FHU_SPERM_LIST	Sperm inside Player
$FHU_SLIF	Inflation Framework
$FHU_SLIF_HELP	If you want to link Fill Her Up to SL Inflation Framework, toggle it on.
$FHU_SENDEVENT_CRITERION	Send Sperm data Criterion
$FHU_SENDEVENT_CRITERION_HELP	A starting rate degree(cum inflation) where the data sent to external pregnancy mods.
$FHU_SENDEVENT_CHANCE	Send Sperm data Chance
$FHU_SENDEVENT_CHANCE_HELP	The chance to send sperm data to external pregnancy mods.
$FHU_MORPHSLIF	Use SLIF 01
$FHU_MORPHSLIF2	Use SLIF 02
$FHU_MORPHSLIF3	Use SLIF 03
$FHU_MORPHSLIF4	Use SLIF 04
$FHU_MORPH_SLIF_HELP	Sending morph data to SLIF. If it's off, NIO will manage the data. If the morph slider is used by other mods, make sure to toggle it on.
$FHU_MORPH_DISABLED	Please reset all the actors before make changes.
$FHU_REMOVESPERMVAG_AMOUNT	Sperm Removal Amount(Vaginal)
$FHU_REMOVESPERMVAG_AMOUNT_HELP	How much cum(Vaginal) to remove every loop interval.
$FHU_REMOVESPERMANAL_AMOUNT	Sperm Removal Amount(Anal)
$FHU_REMOVESPERMANAL_AMOUNT_HELP	How much cum(Anal) to remove every loop interval.
$FHU_REMOVESPERMORAL_AMOUNT	Sperm Removal Amount(Oral)
$FHU_REMOVESPERMORAL_AMOUNT_HELP	How much cum(oral) to remove every loop interval.

